<package>
	<id>com.udevs.bakgrunnur</id>
	<name>Bakgrunnur</name>
	<version>1.1.1.1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>13.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package><![CDATA[
			mobilesubstrate
			]]>
		</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Truly backgrounding your apps</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
            <b>Truly backgrounding your apps!</b><br/><br/>
            Bakgrunnur is a backgrounding (or I should say foregrounding) tweak that will make your apps run infinitely in the background. It even works when your device is locked! Good thing about Bakgrunnur is that you have total control over how your apps should run. When people say they want the apps to run forever in the background, they don't really mean what they mean. Most of the time they want the apps to run in the background for a certain duration before it's being terminated by iOS. Bakgrunnur can do just that!<br/><br/>
            
            <b>Features:</b><br/>
            <ul>
            <li>Expiration time for each individual app.</li><br/>
            <li>Show indicator on homescreen when the apps is backgrounding by Bakgrunnur</li><br/>
            <li>Option to retire apps gracefully or terminate it when it's expired</li><br/>
            <li>Control center module for easy enabling/disabling</li><br/>
            <li>CLI tool for those scripting nerds (like me)</li><br/>
            </ul>
            <br/>
            <b>This package tested to be working on iOS 13.5. Might or might not work on lower iOS version.</b><br/><br/>
            <br/>
            <br/>
            To support development: <a href="https://www.paypal.me/udevs">https://www.paypal.me/udevs</a>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			-<b>Added sort priority in "Manage Apps"</b><br/>
			-Added "Immortal" option in addtion to retire & terminate<br/>
			-Added force/haptic touch shortcut for each individual app<br/>
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            -<b>Fixed expiration bug introduced in v1.1.0</b><br/>
            -<b>Indicator on Dock now out of beta, it now should update synchronously with homesceeen indicator</b><br/>
            -<b>Fixed indicator not updating if termination is scheduled while screen is locked and app is still visible for eyes during locking</b><br/>
            -<b>Added -F flag for CLI</b><br/>
            -Indicates enabled app in "Manage Apps" using checkmark<br/>
            -Fixed reset didn't invalidate currently all backgrounded apps<br/>
            -Fixed native dots didn't get overriden when dot indicator is preferred<br/>
            -Fixed expiration defaulted to zero when user leaved it empty after editing<br/>
            -Some other fixes for CLI<br/>
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
