<package>
	<id>com.udevs.bakgrunnur</id>
	<name>Bakgrunnur</name>
	<version>1.5.2</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>13.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package><![CDATA[
			mobilesubstrate
			]]>
		</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Truly backgrounding your apps</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
			<big><b>NOT COMPATIBLE WITH VOICECHANGER XS</b></big><br/><br/>
			
            <b>Truly backgrounding your apps!</b><br/><br/>
            Bakgrunnur is a backgrounding (or should I say foregrounding) tweak that will make your apps run infinitely in the background. It even works when your device is locked! Good thing about Bakgrunnur is that you have total control over how your apps should run. When people say they want the apps to run forever in the background, they don't really mean what they mean. Most of the time they want the apps to run in the background for a certain duration before it's being terminated by iOS. Bakgrunnur can do just that!<br/><br/>
            
            <b>Features:</b><br/>
            <ul>
            <li>Expiration time for each individual app.</li><br/>
            <li>Show indicator on homescreen when the apps is backgrounding by Bakgrunnur</li><br/>
            <li>Option to retire apps gracefully or terminate it when it's expired, or keeps it alive forever</li><br/>
            <li>Option to retire apps based on CPU usage</li><br/>
            <li>Control center module for easy enabling/disabling</li><br/>
            <li>Quick action (force/haptic touch menu) for each individual app on homescreen</li><br/>
            <li>CLI tool. <i>"bkg -h"</i> for more details</li><br/>
            </ul>
            <br/>
            <b>This package tested to be working on iOS 13.5. Might or might not work on lower iOS version.</b><br/><br/>
            <br/>
            <br/>
            To support development: <a href="https://www.paypal.me/udevs">https://www.paypal.me/udevs</a>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•Added network (download/upload speed) feature for Advanced mode<br/>
			•Added "Enable/Disable Once" in quick action menu & control center module. Off by default. Your previously configured setting for this particular section was reset, reconfigure if needed.<br/>
			•Added expandable module view for a list of full actions when long press. Enabled by default, configure in control center settings.
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •Uncluttered settings UI<br/>
            •Fixed indicator not updated for folder<br/>
            •Some bug fixes & improvements
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
