<changelog>
	<changes>
		<version>1.1.2</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•None
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •Fixed not working properly for some users<br/>
            •Few other fixes
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changes><changes>
		<version>1.1.1.2</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•None
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •Quick fix for Arabic localization<br/>
            •Added Simplified Chinese (xiehq) localization
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changes><changes>
		<version>1.1.1.1</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•None
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •More precisely stop charging at designated level<br/>
            &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp‣Sometimes you'll notice that the charged percentage overshooted by around 1-2% more than the preferred max charge level and that's perfectly normal. iOS occasionally decides not to update the percentage until the next cycle, especially when the device is in very deep sleep. Moreover, the pecentage that shows is just an estimation by iOS itself and is not absolute accurate numerically. However, BattSafe has already trying its best in intelligently mitigating this<br/>
            •Fixed notification occasionally dispatched more than once<br/>
            •Re-notify after a respring while power connected<br/>
            •Added Arabic (peterfectionn) localization<br/>
            •If you wish to contribute in localizing in your local language, submit pull request at <a href="https://github.com/udevsharold/BattSafe-Localization">https://github.com/udevsharold/BattSafe-Localization</a>
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changes><changes>
		<version>1.1.0</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•Added option to show notification when max charge level reached<br/>
			•Added action to continue charging from the notification center(force/haptic touch)
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •Fixed stop charging not working as intended on some devices<br/>
            •Fixed sometimes the charging level overshoot by few percent above preferred max charge level<br/>
            •Dismiss keyboard when scrolling in Preferences
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changes><changes>
		<version>1.0.0</version>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•First release
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •None
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changes>
</changelog>
