<package>
	<id>com.udevs.nanofi</id>
	<name>NanoFi</name>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>12.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package><![CDATA[
			mobilesubstrate
			]]>
		</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Make Apple Watch data transfer rate from iPhone go brrrrrrrr</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Speed up data transfer from iOS to Apple Watch rate. By default, Apple Watch prioritized Bluetooth connection, which makes transferring of music etc. very slow. NanoFi attempts to make WiFi as default connection. Note that your Apple Watch needs to be connected to local WiFi network (autojoin) for this to work. Please read the description in Settings for more info. It comes with a Control Center module. The module acts as an intermediate switch where sometimes the request to utilize WiFi failed due to Apple Watch not responsive to our request and you might want to re-request the operation. I have no control over this without knowing how watchOS works internally, this is the best I could do.<br/><br/>
			
			<big><b>How to use this tweak?</b></big><br/>
You’ll have to activate NanoFi via the CC module (the switch in Settings.app just act an master switch that will completely disable the tweak) it acts as an indicator of whether we successfully switch to wifi link. If it’s not, the module will automatically revert back to off. It might failed for various reasons, one of it is your Apple Watch not responding (no handshake) to our request for switching. Hence, that’s where the toggle comes in.<br/><br/>
            
            This package tested to be working on iPhone X iOS 14.3, and with Apple Watch S5 on watchOS 7.3.3. Might or might not work on different combinations.<br/><br/>
            
            To support development: <a href="https://www.paypal.me/udevs">https://www.paypal.me/udevs</a>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•If you're v0.1.1 user, this is a completely new tweak that does the same thing. The approach was changed. See release post for more info.
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
            •None
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
