<package>
	<id>com.udevs.vexillarius</id>
	<name>vexillarius</name>
	<version>0.0.1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>14.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package><![CDATA[
			mobilesubstrate<br/>
			rocketbootstrap
			]]>
		</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Standard Bearer</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
            <b>Standard Bearer</b><br/><br/>
            We assume that all oranges are orange in color because of their name, 
            the fruit is often green when ripe, thanks to plenty of chlorophyll. 
            In South America and other tropical locales, oranges are green year round. 
            But in the U.S., where it's colder, oranges lose their chlorophyll and take 
            on the color that matches their name. And because North American shoppers 
            are used to oranges that are actually orange, imported fruit is either exposed 
            to ethylene gas or shocked with cold water in order to remove the chlorophyll. Since
            we're on the topic of food, should we debates over whether or not pineapple 
            has any place on a pizza?? Fun fact, the Hawaiian pizza originally came from Chatham, Ontario, Canada!
            Restaurant owner Sam Panopoulos was born in Greece but moved to Canada when he was 20 years old.
            And in 1962, the entrepreneur decided to put pineapple on pizza. Panopoulos, who passed away in 
            2017, once told the BBC, "We just put it on, just for the fun of it, see how it was 
            going to taste. We were young in the business and we were doing a lot of experiments." 
            The name apparently came from the brand of canned pineapple that Panopoulos used on 
            that fateful day he invented the Hawaiian pizza. Thank you for coming to my TED talk, 
            this tweak is a helper for displaying banner.
            <br/>
            <br/>
            To support development: <a href="https://www.paypal.me/udevs">https://www.paypal.me/udevs</a>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change><![CDATA[
			<b>NEW FEATURES:</b><br/>
			•First release
			<br/><br/>
            <b>FIXES & IMPROVEMENTS:</b><br/>
        	•None
            ]]>
		</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
